HELLO?, THIS VIDEO WILL SHOW YOU HOW TO APPLY FOR A LEAVE...
AND PLAN A LEAVE(LEAVE PLANNER)
STARTING FROM THE LOGIN PAGE ENTER YOUR CREDENTIALS,
TO LOG IN INTO YOUR ACCOUNT...
YOU WILL LAND ON THIS PAGE- THE DASHBOARD -
NEXT CLICK THE DROP DOWN MENU ICON ON THE FAR TOP LEFT..
HOVER YOUR MOUSE OVER LEAVE
TRANSACTION THEN LEAVE APLLICATION AS SHOWN
YOU WILL SEE ALL YOUR LEAVE APPLIED HERE AND THEIR STATUS
TO APPLY FOR A NEW LEAVE CLICK THE ADD BUTTON
SELECT TYPE OF LEAVE(E.G ANNUAL LEAVE)
CHOOSE THE DATE YOUR LEAVE STARTS
AND THE DATE THE LEAVE  ENDS
ADD A COMMENT
CONTACT INFORMATION WHILE ON LEAVE
CLICK SAVE TO COMMIT YOUR LEAVE APPLICATION
TO CONFIRM YOUR LEAVE APPLICATION
GO TO YOUR DASHBOARD YOUR LEAVE WILL BE LISTED HERE